question_data = [{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
                 ,{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with &quot;Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials and Tribulations&quot; as its final game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, you can upgrade the &quot;Apothicon Servant&quot; in the &quot;Shadows Of Evil&quot; map.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]